https://scantronltd.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Browse:Privacy PolicyIntroductionThis privacy policy sets out how Scantron Industrial Products Ltd uses and protects any information that you give to us when you use this website, in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679.  Scantron Industrial Products Ltd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.Scantron Industrial Products Ltd may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 25/05/2018.If you have any questions about how we use your data, please contact us by e-mail:  scantron@scantronltd.co.uk using the subject line ‘Data Protection’.What we collectWe may collect the following information:name, company and job titlecontact information including email address and telephone numberdemographic information such as address and postcodeany other information given in the free textWhenever we store any of your personal information, we will always ask for your explicit consent and provide you with a link to this privacy policy.For information on what we do with this data and why it is collected, please see the section below “What we do with the information we gather”.CookiesA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.Scantron uses a number of different cookies on this site including core, functional cookies that are required for the correct operation of the site and tracking cookies that help us to monitor and improve the site for its users.We do not store any third party advertising cookies.Disabling CookiesIf you are not comfortable with us storing cookies, there are a couple of options that you can take when using our site:-Most web browsers will allow you to disable all cookies or just third party cookies.  Instructions on how to do this for various browsers can be found here.  If you completely disable cookies our website may not function as intended.You can browse our site using your browser’s anonymous browsing mode, for example Chrome’s ‘incognito’ mode or Internet Explorer’s ‘inPrivate browsing’ mode.  This will prevent the site from reading any older cookies, or storing any cookies for longer than your session duration.What we do with the information we gatherWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:Internal record keepingTo improve our products and servicesTo contact you about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have providedFrom time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mailData RetentionWe will store your personal data on record and process it in accordance with this privacy policy until you either withdraw consent or because there is no legitimate reason for us to retain this data.SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Controlling your personal informationYou may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the boxes that you can tick to indicate that you are happy for us to keep your details on record and/or share your details with a third partyif you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at scantron@scantronltd.co.ukWe will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.Under the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016-679, you may request details of personal information which we hold about you or request that we update the details that we hold about you.In order to action such a request, please e-mail us at scantron@scantronltd.co.uk or write to Scantron Industrial Products, Monarch Centre, Venture Way, Taunton, Somerset, TA2 8DEIf you believe that any information we are holding about you is incorrect or incomplete, please write or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.Privacy Policy
